MISS ADRENALINE: A TALE OF TWINS
For Christmas...
I'd always ask my parents for a sibling.
Listen, I know that...
I am a very privileged woman,
but I've always felt so alone.
What do you mean? And your parents?
They're really nice, you know?
I love them very much.
But, well...
they travel a lot.
Oh, well, your dad seems like a good guy.
He's also yours.
Excuse me?
No. No, ma'am.
A dad's someone who raises their kids,
who's there for them.
Not someone who does that shit
to the mother of his kids.
Do you want me to tell you
what actually happened, Laura?
Your dad kidnapped you
and told you lies your whole life.
And he told my mom that you had died
in the cruelest way possible.
-And he abandoned me...
-Romina! Enough.
Enough?
-Stop.
-No. I won't stop.
Let's go to his house
and see if he lies to our face.
Look, Romina,
the time to confront Sergio will come.
Don't worry.
What's important is that we're together
and we can get to know each other.
You know what?
I never asked my mom for a sibling.
But I always felt like...
something was missing.
You know what? I completely understand.
Because I felt the same.
It's like...
missing someone I didn't even know.
And now I have you in front of me
and it's...
it's like knowing
that's exactly what was missing.
It was that.
No remorse. Break into her house
and shoot her. That's it.
That's it, right? Very easy.
What's wrong with you? Don't be stupid.
Who reported us
in front of the journalists?
-Romina.
If something happens to that girl,
we'll be the first suspects.
And now there are more cops in the area.
All the patrols fucked up
a bunch of payments I had.
We have to think this through,
we can't fuck it up.
This has to look like an accident.
You get me?
Another thing, Leo can't find out
what we're going to do.
He's a spineless idiot.
I don't want him to snitch.
We need to get this girl now.
Got it, boss.
Laurita, I think it's best we leave.
It's getting late.
Rubencho, I think
I'm going to be a little longer.
Girl, listen to him.
You should leave before it gets dark
because it gets dangerous over here.
Alright, Rubén. Wait for me, I'm coming.
Can you give me
you and your mom's phone number?
Thanks.
What? Is this how you
say goodbye to your sister?
No, ma'am, how silly of you!
Come here.
Oh my God, it can't be.
Laurita, right now,
you have to think this through,
analyze what that lady told you.
That lady, Rubén, is my real mother.
I don't understand.
I don't get how my dad
could be capable of something like this.
But we don't know for sure
if things happened as they said.
Rubén, he told my real mother
that I was dead!
That I was dead, my God!
That I was stillborn, Jesus Christ!
And now, the person I thought
was my mom my whole life,
I have no idea if she knows,
if she has anything to do with this.
I didn't grow up with my sister.
I have a twin sister
and I didn't grow up with her. Why?
To grow up raised by the nannies?
By the nannies? Was that it, Rubén?
Calm down, please.
You have a lot to process right now.
And no matter what, Mr. Sergio is your dad
and Mrs. Virginia raised you.
They love you.
You have to consider that a little, right?
What, Mom?
Are we not going to talk about it?
Talk about what, Romina?
I told you everything I had to say.
That's that.
Well, you can tell me how you feel.
How are you with...?
That man's a bastard, Romina!
-A bastard, I'm so stupid.
-Mom, enough, enough.
Mom, enough.
Enough.
Look at me, look at me.
I want you to know
that none of this is your fault.
None of this, Mom.
That jerk's the one to blame.
And I promise you
that he's gonna pay
for what he did to you.
For all he did. I swear.
Laurita,
as you can see, you have a visitor.
I don't want to see anyone, Rubén.
But you have to go in
and act like nothing's wrong,
because if they ask questions
and see your face, what will you say?
Nothing.
We're not gonna tell anyone, Rubén.
This has to stay between us two,
at least until I talk to my dad.
You can count on me, Laurita.
Thanks, Rubén.
-Get some rest.
-Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Listen, I know how to get your dad
to respond in court.
How?
Get this. If we find the nurse
who cared for my mom,
we'll confirm how things happened
and we'll prove everything your dad did.
And, in doing so, you can also confirm
that your dad isn't a saint.
But I never said that I believed that.
Oh, well, make it crystal clear, then.
Otherwise it'll be my mom's word
against that kidnapper's.
If he hires a powerful lawyer,
we're screwed. You know that.
Miss Laura,
don't forget that Santi and Miss Mariana
are waiting for you.
Okay.
-Thanks, Luzma.
-My pleasure.
I have to go.
-Hi, my love.
-Hi, honey.
SERGIO VÉLEZ TALK ABOUT HIS MARRIAGE
FOR THE FIRST TIME
SERGIO VÉLEZ WINS BIG
AT THE ENTREPRENEUR DREAM AWARDS
WANT TO GO OUT? I WANT TO SEE YOU.
Coming!
Hello.
I was just about to go look for you, but...
How's this?
-Sweetie.
-Yes?
I don't feel good.
-Oh, you were serious?
-Yes.
I thought you made it up
to get rid of Mari.
Uh-uh.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
Oh, well.
-Want to go to sleep?
-Yes.
-Good night.
-Water?
-Yes.
Oof.
I'm not complaining or anything like that,
but I have to ask.
What was that?
What happened? It was so sudden, so nice.
My God.
Okay.
What happened to you?
Are you okay?
Well, no, I'm not exactly okay.
Tell me how I can help.
How can we fix it? Let's do it right now.
Listen, mister, calm down.
You can't solve everything for me.
But...
I appreciate your concern.
I don't like to see you sad or downcast.
Tell me what's going on.
Why talk about that now?
Let's not talk about it.
Look, I already feel better
just by being here with you. Hmm?
I feel better too, with you here with me.
But that means
you're not going to tell me, right?
Trust me.
It's...
family problems, that's all.
Alright.
Don't tell me you're having problems
with my mother-in-law
because if that's the case, sorry,
but I'll have to take her side.
-Oh yeah?
-Yes.
Oh yeah?
Oh yeah? You're shameless!
-Alright, alright, alright.
-Oh yeah?
I bet it's very difficult,
seeing as her daughter is so much work.
Besides,
Mrs. Yesenia, so cute,
all calm and easygoing.
Don't be so sure.
Mrs. Yesenia has a temper too.
Oh, yes, I believe it,
because all of this fire
had to come from somewhere.
Or maybe it came from your dad's side.
Because, by the way, you...
you've never told me
anything about your dad.
Cristóbal, I only have a mom.
Come here, come here, come here.
Look, sorry...
Do you forgive me?
I didn't know
it was a sensitive topic for you.
I promise I won't mention him again, okay?
It's okay.
It's okay. I'm not mad at you.
-Are you really not mad at me?
-No.
Besides, I can't get mad at you.
Why not?
Because I love you.
I love you too.
Romi...
Hmm?
I've never felt
this way about anyone, okay?
Me neither.
Really?
SONIA MENDIGAÑA IN SAMACÁ
Rubén, um...
Can I ask you a favor?
I need you to find the nurse
who took care of Yesenia.
I'll send you the information I have.
Honey, are you okay?
Yes! Coming!
How are you?
Kind of nauseous.
-Oh.
-Mm.
-Were you talking on the phone?
-No it was...
I was watching a video to distract myself.
Okay.
Did I wake you up? Sorry.
-Sorry, sorry.
-No, it's okay.
Want me to look for something
for your tummy?
-No, no.
-A pill?
-Nothing?
-No, let's go to sleep.
-Let's go to sleep.
-Okay.
Come here.
You know what, Romina?
I've been thinking that you are so mad,
and I understand,
because, obviously, I feel the same way,
but I think that we could use this
in a different way.
I don't know, transform it,
make it something happy, joyful,
because, in the end,
it's now the three of us.
Look, I promise that all three of us
will decide what to do together.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Promise?
-I promise.
-Really?
-Really.
Alright.
So change that face, then.
Like you said, it's us three now,
and Mom, I promise you, that, from now on,
only good things will happen for us.
I swear.
God bless you, honey.
Listen carefully.
We're going to follow that girl
until we know where she goes and when.
And when we know that,
you already know what to do.
Heads up, Nuche.
We're on alert.
We can't follow her.
She went into the second one, hurry!
She's got it figured out.
She sells empanadas in the morning.
She changes her afternoon routine
according to her clients.
It's tough following her
because she goes everywhere on that bike.
She goes into little alleys
where cars can't even fit.
We won't touch that girl until we know
everything she does in the hood,
because we're doing the hit
in our territory.
-Okay?
-Yes.
Romi. Romi, wait. Romi, come here!
Come here. I was telling the truth.
I'll leave all this shit behind, okay?
Leo, I'm not telling you anything.
Romi, I know you.
Besides, when I make a promise, I keep it.
Leo,
honestly, I couldn't care less
about what you do with your life.
But I'll tell you one thing, kid.
Sometimes, blood is thicker than water.
Come on, Romi, let's talk.
-Come on.
-Be careful, kid.
No, Laurita, it's not good news.
No one in this town
knows anyone named Sonia Mendigaña.
There is no record of her
working at the hospital.
Unbelievable.
Well, hardly, Laurita,
because it's been almost 20 years.
It's possible she was only hired
to assist in the birth, you know.
She's probably not even from here.
Well, don't worry, Rubén.
Just come back
because I don't want my dad to find out
that you left
and tell you off because of me.
We'll talk. Thanks, bye.
-Good morning, sweetie.
-Hello.
-How are you?
-Good.
I love how that sweater looks on you.
And the pants.
-Good morning, excuse me.
-Good morning.
-Hello, Luzma.
-How are you, ma'am?
Good.
I like your boots too.
I think it's your favorite look.
-Excuse me, enjoy!
-Thanks.
Thanks, Luzma.
Yes, you're prettier than ever.
I'm really in love with you.
You're the prettiest girl I've ever seen.
-I'm being a bit intense, right? Yes.
-No, honey.
-No, that's not it. Honey, I'm tired.
-Yes, I feel...
I understand.
I feel like I'm suffocating you
a little bit
these days, and I think I should leave.
Don't be like that, Santi.
I think you need time to be alone
and I'm feeling the same way,
because it's not good to feel like this.
Besides, I have a meeting in Santa Marta.
I wanted you to come
to the beach for a couple of days,
but I don't think it's a good idea.
I think a bit of space is a better idea.
-So that's that, then.
-You're overexaggerating things.
I'm not exaggerating. I'm gonna go.
-I'm gonna go.
-Honey, don't go like this.
-Bye. It's okay.
-Santi, don't go...
I need to break away from my brothers
or Romina won't trust me.
That's gonna be hard.
Not just because
your brothers won't let you,
but because you and Romi are done.
For real. That happened a while back, bro.
It hasn't been a while.
She's furious with Marlon.
No.
Once I tell her everything's set
so we can leave, it'll change.
That's when everything's gonna change
for my Romi.
That's what I'm working on, Estiven.
What? Working on what?
From what I can see, you're still working
day and night with your brothers, right?
Yes, but the commission went up.
But my brothers don't know that yet.
A pleasure, sir. We are at your service.
I feel horrible
about lying to my boyfriend, Romi.
No, girl, I understand.
I'm going through the same thing
with my Whiz.
Is that his name?
No.
Can you imagine?
No, his name is Cristóbal Ruiz.
But he's great at his job,
so that's what he's known by in the hood.
Well, my Santi is also amazing.
Oh, yeah?
Isn't he one of those pretty boys?
Oh, Laura, don't get upset,
I'm just messing with you.
I'm sure that guy's as cool as you.
Mmm.
Either way,
I didn't call about that, Romi.
I didn't find out anything
about the nurse.
But relax, I'll look around here at home.
And what are you looking for?
Honestly, I have no idea.
Anyways, I have to be careful,
because if one of the employees finds out
I'm going through my dad's things,
they'll go and say something.
Oh, no. Really,
I like him more and more every day.
Well, we'll talk later. Bye.
Okay.
Marriage...
From the old man down here.
There's money missing.
Oh, yes.
He wasn't able to pay all the interest.
So what? Do I start crying or what?
Come on, bro.
Things are really hard out there.
This guy has always paid on time.
I gave him until next week. That's all.
No, not until next week. I'm writing here
that the client's your problem.
You take care of it.
Come on, Benny.
You know I get along better
with people than with all of you
who scare them like Marlon does.
Oh, what's this? The psychologist.
Is that what they say?
-Not true.
-Like they say out there.
Talking it out is better than war.
Remember that.
Hmm? How about you just charge them
what they owe?
Quit talking shit. Give me Gloria's.
It's here. This is Gloria's.
Alright then, Romi.
I haven't found anything strange here.
And now I have to clean up this mess.
So annoying.
Bad luck.
Come on, then,
let's talk about something else.
Are we gonna see each other again?
I'd love to.
Besides,
there's a bunch of stuff
I want to tell you.
But you know what?
It's better if we meet up
at a different place.
So we don't go calling attention to us
with that Land Rover of yours.
I have the perfect place
where we can see each other.
I'll send it to you.
Go ahead.
Sir, right here, right here.
Thanks, all good.
Rubencho!
What's up?
-They're waiting for you.
-Great seeing you. Yeah? Oh, good.
This place is empty.
Laura!
Lau!
Romi?
-Girl!
-Over here, go on.
Wow!
And I present to you...
my baby.
My first bakery.
The idea is to become independent
from my parents with this place
and, eventually,
be able to live off of this.
Laura, this place is amazing.
-And it's yours?
-No.
I've just paid the down payment,
and we'll go from there.
And how'd you do that?
Saving up.
And working, a lot.
I invested every dollar
I've ever made into this place.
My wages, my allowances, my bonuses.
Everything.
Girl, I've also saved my whole life,
but I can't afford
to change the brakes on my bike.
Relax, Romi,
we're going to change that together.
Oh, listen to this girl. Uh-uh.
No, no ma'am.
Okay, crazy, just walk
and I'll show you the kitchen.
It's actually finished.
-Over here?
-Yes. Go ahead.
Let's put on music.
Oh...
Laura, no, what's with the boring music?
No, I'm gonna show you the good stuff.
No!
No, I can't concentrate with that music.
Okay, so here, we'll make a deal.
We each get one.
Deal, but I'll start then.
Romi.
It's just...
I feel like I've known you my whole life.
Well, it's true.
Don't you see that you and I
met each other in my mom's belly?
Alright, time to bake.
Go on, because I'm getting hungry.
-What else do we need? Okay...
-I'll help.
Mmm!
No! No, no, no, Laura.
Oh my God, what is this?
I have no words.
Oh my God, this is so good.
Mmm.
Girl, that talent came from my mom.
Seriously!
You guys are the exact same,
both of you are amazing chefs!
Ha!
Good to know.
Look.
This is for Yesenia.
Ah!
I can't promise
this is gonna make it home in one piece.
Romi,
I want you and Yesenia
to be my guests of honor
the day I open the shop.
And I hope by that day,
we will have spoken to my dad,
and have resolved everything...
Well, Lau, that's...
It's best if you don't give him a chance
to come and tell you what to do.
In other words, if you call him,
don't tell him about this.
Yeah?
Promise?
I promise.
Nuche already confirmed that the girl
is hanging around with that cop.
Another snitch we'll have to clean out.
But later,
because first, Romina.
What's up?
-What's up, bro?
-What's up?
What are you up to?
Hard at work, not that you'd know it.
What are you working on?
On whatever we need
to get this family ahead, right, Benny?
Important things.
Family things.
See you later.
See ya.
Well, welcome.
Wow, what a beautiful place!
Did you make this all yourself?
Let's say I did,
but I've had a lot of help.
Oh, don't be modest.
How impressive, you're opening a business
all by yourself, and so young!
Very brave.
What's wrong? Why do you make that face?
My dad has never said that.
Sometimes it's like...
it's like I've never been good enough
for him.
Sweetie.
Let me tell you something.
You're an amazing woman.
And don't ever let anyone
tell you otherwise, okay?
And for whatever it's worth,
I'm very proud of you.
A few more steps, careful.
There, there, there.
Ready? Can I open my eyes?
Ready.
You don't like it?
Romi, this is beautiful.
Look, I don't know,
but if I ever leave this place,
I'm taking this wall with me.
Oh, don't be so dramatic!
Honey, it looks wonderful.
You're such an artist, Romi.
You haven't seen anything yet.
My Romina is very talented.
Oh, I know. Like with the bike.
Remember we met
because of that news story.
And thank God.
Listen, Laura. Thanks for this.
No, thanks to you.
Aw!
Romina, you definitely
never cease to amaze me.
-Laura.
-Hmm?
-Can I see the kitchen?
-Of course.
-Where is it?
-Over here.
Oh, okay, great.
I also wanted to tell you
that I gave Rubén the coordinates
to a place I want to take you
because I have a surprise for you.
What?
Another one?
But don't say anything to my mom
because she'll get worried.
And why would she get worried?
It's just...
No, no, no. What a kitchen!
My dream kitchen. Did you see it, Romina?
-Oh, how's the kitchen? Cool, right?
-This place is beautiful.
-And ready to welcome you.
-Thanks, honey.
-Thanks.
-See how happy you look?
This is how you should always be,
happy, you know?
Rubén, do you know that there's something
still on my mind?
What?
That we haven't found out anything
to prove what my dad did.
Well...
I've been looking,
and I'm going to the hospitals
near Samacá to see if I find anything.
Thanks, Rubén.
You know that if we don't find anything,
we'll have to keep looking.
Yes, but for what?
I don't know.
It won't turn on
and I can't find the charger.
Gregorio, my godson, has a computer shop.
He can figure it out.
-That's a good idea.
-Of course.
Alright.
-Thanks.
-Oh, wait!
That girl Romina told me
to give this to you
and that later I'll take you
to a place she told me about.
Okay. Thanks, Rubén.
Wow!
That outfit looks great on you, girl.
Still, I feel super uncomfortable.
Uh-uh. You relax,
I'm going to make you a pro.
-Walk.
-Okay.
Alright, kid, we'll start with this drop
so you can see what it's like.
Romi, I even fall out of bed sometimes.
Oh, but you know how to ride a bike.
Right? Yes!
-No, I do know, but...
-If not, you didn't have a childhood.
Don't worry about it, kid.
You taught me how to make desserts,
I'll teach you how to be a cycling champ.
Check it out.
Wild, Romi!
Come on, kid, it's your turn now.
Me?
Oh my God.
No, no. Wait, okay.
I'm okay now.
What happened, dear?
-What happened? Where are you hurt?
-Oh!
-Where?
-Here.
Does it hurt a lot?
No.
No, no, no.
Oh, be careful, Rubén.
Don't worry.
I'm not that fragile, Romina.
Oh, no. What will we do
with a pastry chef-cyclist?
You'll have to stop her, Rubén.
Listen, you're actually hurt.
Look at that face.
It's not that.
It's because I just decided
not to go to Paris with Santiago.
What? You're going to Paris?
-When?
-I was going to Paris.
Come on, help me, Rubén.
Romina...
I don't want to get separated again
from you or my mom.
I like how you think, kid.
Still, you know that
we'll be together forever.
-Whatever happens.
-Together forever.
-So your godson works here?
-No, it's his business.
-Oh yeah?
-Of course.
Wow.
This is Gregorio, the go-to man
for computer problems, internet issues,
anything like that.
-Nice to meet you. Laura.
-A pleasure, Gregorio Restrepo.
You can call me Gregor.
Everyone calls me that.
Okay.
Um...
Can I have my hand back?
Please? Thanks.
So, were you able to turn on the tablet?
Did you find anything?
Good news: nothing offensive,
no naked photos, nothing like that.
Here is what I found.
BILL STATEMENTS
I don't understand. These are...
Deposits. Yes.
Deposits that were made
since around the year 2000.
Huh?
Is there a way of seeing the date
a deposit was made?
Yes, look, right here.
It's this whole column.
The first one
was made on November 10th, 2001,
to a Sonia Mendigaña.
Everything's ready for Romina.
You just have to say when.
Later this afternoon, bro.
Just do it.
We'll do it when she drinks her juice
at Gilbert's stand.
After practice?
That girl doesn't change her routine.
And it's going to cost her her life.
-All set.
-Whiskey?
Of course.
But pour me a double.
-Hey! Hey, kid!
-Oh, "kid"? Yeah right!
-Come here, wait!
-"Kid" was when we were together. No!
I have to tell you something. My brothers
want to kill you. Listen to me.
What?
After practice at the juice stand.
I'm serious.
We have to do something.
Let's leave and go somewhere safe.
If you stick with me,
nothing'll happen to you. Let's go.
My mom. No, I have to go get my mom.
-Romina!
-I have to go get my mom.
-No, no, we have to leave!
-Leo!
If they don't find me,
they're going to kill my mom, right?
Okay, alright. So let's go get your mom.
-No, hold on. Hold on.
-Okay, okay. All good.
-What do we do?
-Um...
You told me it was after practice, right?
-Yes.
-Alright.
So we still have a few hours. So...
I'll go get my mom by myself.
If they see us together,
it'll be a disaster.
They'll fuck us both up.
You go on and act normal.
No tickets, no problems, nothing.
I get my mom, my things, and I'll meet you
outside the neighborhood.
Alright. Okay. sounds good, sounds good.
You've got this.
Nothing's gonna happen to you, I promise.
Not to you nor your mom, baby, I swear.
All good. Watch your back. Go on!
"Watch your back."
My dad paid that woman
for her silence, Rubén.
Look. This...
is the proof that this man is everything
Romina and Yesenia believed to be true.
Oh!
Speak of the devil, look who's calling.
Look. Hmm? Right on the dot.
Uh-oh.
If I talk to him right now,
I'll tell him everything.
And I'm not going to give him the chance
to cover things up
like he always does, we know how he is.
I'm not going to answer.
FEDERAL POLICE
You stay over here.
I'll get your mom and get protection
after you file the report.
-No.
-Yes.
No. I didn't tell you to go and do this.
If I leave and run away,
we lose our one real chance
at catching Marlon.
I know you want to be the bait,
but that is not going to happen.
Yes, it will.
-I don't want anything to happen to you.
-I'm going to be fine.
You know that this is our chance
to finally get rid of those guys.
-Do you understand how dangerous this is?
-Of course.
We both know that there are times
where you have to risk it all to win big.
And this is one of those.
But you know what?
I'm very calm.
Because I know the best police sergeant
will be taking care of me.
Sergeant Whiz.
I truly believe in you.
Completely.
Believe in me.
Have faith.
You have to keep up your usual routine.
That way, they won't suspect a thing.
Go to practice
and then the juice stand, like always.
-Are we clear?
-Clear, Sergeant.
Smile for me.
Everything's gonna be okay. I promise.
I know everything's gonna be okay.
-I'll be there to watch over you, okay?
-I know.
I know.
Where are we going, huh?
With whose money? With whose permission?
I'm going to go with Estiven
and his friends. Why?
-Nuche saw you talking with Romina.
-So?
Now I have to ask for permission
to talk to someone?
-What did you blab about?
-About what? What's going on?
I already told you, you rat!
I told you if you betrayed this family,
she'd be the one who pays.
Be thankful you're my brother,
otherwise you'd already be dead.
-Relax, Marlon.
-Like Romina's about to be.
Marlon, no, no. Leave Romina alone.
Please, Marlon, come on.
Leave Romina alone.
She's gonna leave. Don't mess with her.
Come on! Marlon! Marlon!
Leave her alone! Come on, Marlon!
-Marlon!
-Quit yelling, stop fucking it up.
-Marlon. Marlon, wait.
-What do you want?
Look. If Leo found out
what we were gonna do and he told her,
he's fucked it all up.
We're not gonna waste any more time.
It's the perfect time.
So, what? Is it still on?
It's the best time to catch them
for attempted homicide.
Yes, but we are risking a civilian's life.
We'll have multiple officers nearby.
I'll be in charge of the operation.
I promise I won't let anything bad
happen to Romina Páez.
We're talking about
capturing Marlon Chitiva,
the head of the Mafia.
Do you know something, Sergeant?
If this goes south, your career is over.
-And the civilian could lose her life.
-That's why it won't go south.
There is no room for error, sir.
I know.
I need you all focused.
Remember what we talked about
and be ready for anything.
Safety off on the guns, okay?
-Yes, sir, Sergeant!
-Forward!
I CAN'T STAY HERE ANY LONGER.
I'M HEADING TO THE JUICE STAND EARLY.
ALL GOOD. I'M HERE WITH MY PEOPLE.
RECORD OF SAVINGS ACCOUNT DEPOSIT
I'm really sorry.
This must be very hard for you, right?
Deep down you wanted to believe
your dad had nothing to do with it.
But like Romi said,
we can't bury our heads in the sand.
And with this, my dad can't deny anything.
Thanks so much.
Romi will be very happy to see this.
Oh, yes, but she's at practice right now.
Do you want to show her later?
-I...
-No, honey, don't bother.
She turns it off during practice.
She won't answer.
And if we go to the park?
Want to see your sister at practice?
Can I?
Yes, I'll take you. She'll feel so proud.
-And we'll show her then.
-Yes, of course.
-I'll take it.
-Alright.
Let's go, then.
Boss, I just saw Romina
pass by the bridge.
She's with her mom.
The idiot didn't go to practice.
They're going to Fourth Street.
Okay.
-Change of plans.
-Tell me.
Tell Carloncho we're heading
to Fourth Street now.
What? Hurry up.
Hello, Carloncho, what's up?
Marmolejo, copy?
Any updates?
Nothing, Sergeant.
The practice area is right here.
We're really close.
Romina is going to be so happy
when she sees you here.
Mom? Thanks.
POLICE
Station, we need reinforcements.
There's a car accident.
Hey, help me clear the area!
Clear the area!
Valencia, clear the area!
Out of the way!
Clear the area,
there may be another explosion!
Get out of here, it might explode again!
No.
No!
Everyone back off! Back off, please.
Everyone back off.
Romina!
Help! Please!
We need to get everyone out.
Get back, get back, get back!
Get back!
Get back! Ambulance!
Ortega! Ortega!
Station, where's the ambulance
and firefighters?
Get everyone out of here!
Quickly!
Get everyone out of here! Go!
Stop, bro. Where are you going?
-Stop! Stop!
-No!
No!
-No, bro!
Romina, please. No, love, please.
Don't die on me. No, Romina, please.
Please, no.
Breathe, breathe.
Breathe, baby, please. Please, no.
That's it, breathe, please.
Please breathe, Romina.
No!
Romina. Romina, please!
Subtitle translation by: Nancy Cabrera