You're going to love
being their nanny. They're angels.
My children are so well-behaved.
I love them.
Excuse me. Hello?
I'm going to be 15 minutes late
to the presentation.
Santiago, leave me alone! Santiago!
-Santiago, stop!
-What are you doing, Santiago?
Mom, she started it.
She put my shoes in the toilet.
-That's not true, Mom!
-Santiago!
You're grounded, Santiago! Stop!
Sorry! That was meant for Sofia!
Please, don't go!
Don't take it personally.
He just wanted you to try the cake.
I have a meeting in 15 minutes!
I'm not going to make it.
Sorry, my bad!
No.
Tell your mom that I quit.
No, I'm sorry, Mr. Rizo.
I'll be right there.
I had to run an errand at the bank and…
It was a misunderstanding.
So, do you have experience
with energetic children?
I swear it's plastic. I swear.
Leo!
Mr. Rizo… I won't make it.
Did the board members confirm
their attendance at my dad's party?
Yeah.
What about you?
Are you ready to be the new boss?
I just have to finish
the business proposal
that I'm going to present to the board,
and get a new nanny.
Hey.
Oh, Leo.
Ready.
Get out of the kitchen, please.
I'll see you at the office.
Leo, you're going to burn the house down.
It was just an experiment, Mom,
and no one wants to live until they're 40.
Many do, but you probably don't.
He hasn't eaten his lunch
for the last two weeks,
except for the hot dogs.
Because they come out of a package
with listed ingredients.
-But you can't read.
-I learned last year.
Reading your text messages.
Traitor!
I'm going to tell Mom, Dad and everyone!
What am I going to do with these kids?
No, don't even look at me.
You know I don't like children.
If you make me take care of them,
you'll be missing a nanny and a cook.
Don't worry, Martita. Last time I did,
Leo escaped,
you forgot to get Sofia picked up,
and she stayed in school until 8:00 p.m.
Must be the nanny that Romina sent.
Please, let her be maternal,
caring, loving…
Don't tell her about all the others
who didn't want to work with us.
Okay?
Okay.
We have to tell her.
No.
Good morning.
Hi.
Oh… I'm glad you're here.
-I need you to take care of the garden--
-No, Romina sent me.
Your ex-nanny. I thought
I was going to take care of kids.
Romina said she was sending
Gaby, her goddaughter.
Godson. I'm Gabriel.
Gabriel Padilla.
Nice to meet you.
THE MANNY
Sorry, to be honest,
I was expecting someone else.
A woman?
Yes, and I understand.
But believe me,
you have nothing to worry about.
I promise I have a lot of experience.
I helped raise
most of my nieces and nephews.
Besides, there's nothing
a good lasso can't fix.
Did you tie up the kids?
Only when necessary,
and the well was full of water.
A well. Great idea.
Don't even think about it, Marta.
I'm claustrophobic.
I won't leave my kids
with someone like you.
But you were going to
with the five other nannies who said no.
That's not relevant.
I can't have a man in my home.
What will my friends say?
They already talk about the men you bring.
Although you never brought
a cowboy before.
Mom, Santiago wants to upload
a pic of me wearing only a bra.
How many times have I asked you
to respect the privacy of others?
I caught her stuffing her bra.
You're the one who needs to grow a pair.
You're a loser
who's never had a girlfriend!
Sofia, that's not okay. Who's that girl?
Not dating doesn't make you a loser,
it makes you selective.
Who are you, and why are you so wise?
Romina's godson.
Do you know what else is wise?
Changing your mind.
If you post your sister's picture,
the girl you like will think you're rude.
Besides, it's not okay to do that,
especially to your sister.
DELETE?
CANCEL - ACCEPT
Thanks, dude.
Hurry up or you'll be late to school.
Hey!
Are you going to take your sister's bra
to act cool in school?
I swear I didn't know I had it.
Women don't like that.
You have to talk to them openly.
Say something from here.
Tell her she's the star
that lights up your path.
Make her feel special.
Not that you're a womanizer.
I'm doing you a favor.
You would have made a fool of yourself.
Thanks for helping my son.
Truth is, I bribed him
to convince you to hire me.
Just a moment. Okay, you can stay.
As a trial.
Marta, show Gaby
where he's going to sleep.
Yes, I'll be right there.
I need all the account info…
Follow me, handsome.
Howdy!
-If you call me handsome, I'll follow.
-This way.
As soon as possible, please.
You look great, cousin. More than before.
Don't waste
your phony compliments, cousin.
Dad hasn't decided yet
who's going to be the CEO.
Do I have to remind you that I'm a partner
and I have the same rights you do?
You do, but you work
three times less than I do.
Don't get your hopes up, cousin.
Let me give you some advice.
You should improve your attitude,
or you'll never get married.
Oh, my bad!
You did marry Joaquín,
but he left you for Mich,
who is almost twice
as young as you, right?
It doesn't hurt me at all,
so don't even worry.
Actually, why are you here?
It's not payday.
Your dad called me in.
There's a complicated matter
that requires a man like me to resolve it.
You're going to unclog the toilet?
Close, because
there's lots of shit involved.
Shit that a little girl like you
won't clean up, but I can.
Otherwise, and I mean this,
your daddy could lose it all.
What do you mean?
It's confidential.
See you later.
-Hi, Dad.
-Where are you?
What do you mean?
I told you I was coming to Guadalajara.
You kicked me out, right?
What else could I do?
You're my only son, Gabriel.
I trusted you, and you disappointed me.
Yes, that's why I left.
So I can't mess up anymore.
You didn't even take your truck.
I don't know what you were thinking.
Don Mario, come get this truck!
I want to do things differently,
and you won't let me.
How could I?
You kept insisting on alternative feeding,
the pigs were underweight
and I lost a lot of money.
And now, those vulture lenders
want to take my ranch.
I asked you to do something,
and you didn't deliver.
I always deliver on my promises.
But I never agreed to do things
they way you wanted them.
Whatever it was,
you fucked me over, Gabriel.
I'm hanging up
before my pacemaker gives out.
Sure, okay.
I love you, Dad. Take care.
Yeah, okay.
HEY! - EXCLUSIVE
JIMENA LEMUS - "WILL SHE BE THE NEW CEO
OF FINANCIERA LEMUS?"
I just saw that idiot Rogelio.
He said the company is in trouble.
I thought we had a great year
with the clients you brought in.
It's so weird, I don't get it.
WAITING FOR THE KIDS
TO COME BACK FROM SCHOOL.
Oh, no. I need to find a nanny ASAP.
Why?
This is why.
My previous nanny
said she'll send someone,
and she sent me her godson. Why not?
Could he take care of me?
I doubt this guy can take care of anyone.
He used to tie up
his nephews at his ranch.
I bet he couldn't find a job
and Romina wants to stick me with him.
I don't see a problem with it,
on the contrary.
He looks great from all angles.
Hi, sweetheart.
Hi, Dad.
How's my surprise going away party going?
It's ready, but it's not a surprise.
That's my girl!
Did you write my speech?
Yes, I just need you to tell me
who's going to replace you as CEO.
That's a surprise.
Okay. I saw Rogelio a while ago.
Is there something I don't know?
No, he's taking care
of the "Dos Caminos" ranch deal.
They owe us a lot of money.
The future of this company,
and ours depends on their payment.
Things could get difficult.
I get it, but that's my account.
I should take care of it.
No, you should work on my speech.
-I'll send it over shortly.
-Thank you.
Thanks.
I'm sure he's going to choose you.
Oh, no. Sofía just uploaded
a new pic on Instagram.
So what?
What do you mean?
I'm not even divorced yet,
and the kids are posting pictures
of a man I brought into my home.
And what a man!
I don't see anything wrong with it.
I tried to tell Tania
the "star that lights my path" thing,
but I made a fool of myself.
Tania's the one that ignores him.
She's in high school.
She's going to Grandpa's party
because her dad works with him.
How do you know?
She just put it on TikTok,
said she wanted to kill herself.
Let's get ready
so you can talk to her then.
-No way!
-What?
In Tepa, you don't
leave a party without a girl.
Where?
Tepatitlán, Jalisco.
Is that on Maps?
Of course, it's on…
That's not relevant right now.
We should get a suit for your brother.
That's going to be difficult.
Santiago never looks good.
He has SpongeBob arms.
-At least I don't have pimples.
-Me neither!
-Look at your face!
-You two are like fighting roosters.
What's wrong with you?
You have to get along.
-Or you'll take us to the well?
-Not at all.
But I'll tell you something.
One day, you're going to be old,
and you're going to need someone
to push your wheelchair.
Leo! What are you doing?
Putting out a fire!
-No! Turn it off!
-Stop it, Leo!
-Wait!
-Leo!
-Your books!
-Shut off!
Joaquín, I need you
to take the kids tonight.
Why is there a guy choking our son?
This is unbelievable.
We're not even divorced yet
and you brought a man home?
Gabriel is Romina's godson,
she sent him to help with the kids,
but he's leaving.
And anyway,
you're already living with someone else!
It will only be for a few days,
until I hire a nanny.
I'd love to, you know I love our kids.
But I'm traveling with Mich
because she opened a new gym.
Is that the sixth gym you open for Mich?
How many gyms
can she be in at the same time?
Unlike you, who's never set foot in one.
Hi, Mich. Bye, Mich.
I don't get why are we here.
I don't think Santiago will find
something to wear here.
Unless we're looking
for a flower print apron.
You might be surprised.
I also wanted to come
because I wanted to see someone.
Are you ready?
Ro-ro-ro-ro-Romina!
Kids!
-Did you escape from home?
-No!
I wish. Mom went crazy since you left.
-Come back, please.
-Oh, sweetie.
Or take us with you.
You'll have to manage
because I'm not coming back.
I always dreamt of having a shop
with products from Gabriel's ranch.
-Gabriel's?
-You have a ranch?
It's my dad's. I rather not talk about it.
Why?
Because Gabriel isn't
what his dad wished he was.
Are you gay?
No. And there wouldn't be
anything wrong with that, Leo.
-See what you did?
-Don't feel down, son.
You're the cutest godson ever.
-We're going to change the world, right?
-That's the goal.
I know what that feels like.
My mom hates that I like the color pink.
Did you know
there are 29,000 tones of pink?
Maybe both of us
should try something different.
Now we need to find something
for Santiago to impress that girl.
Yuck!
What's wrong, Leo? You had never seen one?
-That's where hot dogs come from.
-No!
-Yes.
-No.
Yes. Excuse me, sir.
-Can we take a picture?
-Of course.
-Get ready for a picture.
-Oh, my God.
How's it going, son? Everything okay?
I don't know.
Jimena said this is a trial period.
I don't think I'm going to get the gig.
You have to stay there, Gabriel.
In order to save your dad's ranch,
you have to do whatever is needed.
Go all the way.
I can't find a nanny anywhere.
Did you ask Joaquín for help?
Just don't end up in bed
as it happens every time you meet.
Ha, ha, so funny.
That only happened
once.
Twice.
Three times, max.
And no, he can't do it
because he's traveling with Mich.
Relax.
You'll have to trust
that the handsome cowboy
will be able to control them.
That's the issue,
he's a man, and he's handsome.
I can already see it on Club Social.
"Jimena Lemus brought a man to her home."
Yes, he's handsome, but he's feral.
How could he show a dead body to the kids?
I bet he tied them up to put them to bed.
I would love it if he tied me up.
-Oh, hi, Gaby!
-I'll call you later.
Leo is asleep. No, I didn't tie him up.
Sorry, Gabriel.
I didn't mean for you to hear that.
Which part?
That I'm feral or that I'm handsome?
It's the first time someone calls me that.
That I'm feral.
But I wanted to apologize
for the picture with the pig.
You gotta understand, Gabriel.
Tomorrow's party
is very important to me because
my dad might announce
that I will be the new CEO.
CEO? So, you work for a lender?
Yes.
Wow. That sounds like an important role.
My job allows me to help many people.
That's my dream.
Even if my dad doesn't understand it.
I worked hard for things
to be managed in a different way.
Yes, I understand that.
More than you can imagine.
Okay. How can I help?
Help with the kids. Help with them.
Because, although I want to,
I can't be there for them.
Don't worry, I'll take care of them.
That's why you hired me.
Sure.
-And I'm sorry about--
-Don't worry about it.
I'm used to hearing that I'm handsome.
Good night.
Okay, give it to me!
I won't impress anyone with this.
Especially Tania.
Don't worry, Santi.
You're doing well and learning quickly.
You should try to think
that Tania is the lamp,
and you're throwing
a lasso of love on her.
I'm pretty sure Tania
is going to run away.
Don't underestimate
the power of the lasso.
Try again.
We have to get dressed for the event.
-Okay.
-Okay?
If you get this one,
I'll teach you the golden lasso.
-Two loops…
-One loop, two loops…
There you go.
That one was closer.
What's up, Dad?
We can't find Arete.
The guys said you took her.
Of course, I did.
They were going to kill her.
Because she's not fit for breeding!
We can't keep animals
that doesn't make a profit.
Even less now when those sharks
from the lending company
are conspiring with the government!
I'm not going to give up.
Dad, be careful. I can come back to help.
No, thank you. I can take care of myself.
Look at you!
Are you sure that Tania will notice me?
She's gonna stare at you, that's for sure.
Man, you look amazing.
Remember, it's important to cause
a second first impression.
Besides, there's nothing
a lasso can't fix.
You already know.
-I think it's true that my arms are long.
-Told you.
That's okay.
You can give Tania bigger hugs.
I'll go get Leo.
How are you? Nice to see you.
Thanks for coming.
Please, come in.
-Relax, everything is perfect.
-I know, my dad looks happy.
He looks a hundred times better in person.
-Hi.
-Everything looks great.
Hi, I'm Brenda and I'm single.
Nice to meet you, Brenda.
So nice.
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm trying something new. Less pink.
And I want to create a good impression.
I always dress the same.
-Kids! Sofi, Santi, Leo.
-Hi.
-Nice to meet you. I'm Gabriel.
-Nice to meet you.
-Ernesto Lemus.
The kids were excited to see you,
and to celebrate their mom
as the new CEO of the company.
Nice try!
But the announcement will be a surprise.
Although I'm happy to see
that Jimena has a suitor
who can take her away from work,
so she can take care of her kids.
Dad, Gabriel isn't my boyfriend,
and I'm not looking for someone
to take care of me.
I love to work.
So much, that this year
I took the company to the next level.
-And I appreciate that.
-Mr. Ernesto!
Sorry, I have to go.
He's probably going to choose Rogelio.
Who's Rogelio?
My cousin, who wants
to push me aside to impress my dad,
and it seems to be working.
It was a bad idea to come.
I wish I was wearing black
to match this party.
Kids, it's not your fault
that my dad doesn't trust me, okay?
I have to go greet other people,
and while I'm at it,
throw myself off a ledge.
-Tania is here. What do I do?
-What do you mean?
Go say hi.
Remember, your suit will look better
if you walk proudly,
hold the belt,
and then, hat on.
There you go.
What's up, Tania? How are you doing?
I didn't know it was a costume party.
What a dork!
How embarrassing.
I definitely need a drink.
Wait, Tania!
I have something to say about Santi.
What? That he's in Christian Nodal's band?
No, that he's not like anyone else.
He'll never stop surprising you.
You're right about that.
I'm going to get a drink.
Thanks for trying to help me.
I don't want Leo to push
my wheelchair when I'm old.
What's up, Leo?
We can't let Rogelio
take away the role from my mom.
She deserves it more than anyone.
You should convince your grandpa
that your mom
is the best one for the role.
How? He won't listen to us.
I don't know. Let's think of something.
Hi, good afternoon.
Thank you for being here.
This party is especially
important for me because,
as many of you know,
I'm formally announcing today that
I'm retiring from the company I founded
when, one day, I lent my savings
to my brother, may he rest in peace,
so he could buy a bicycle.
Today is a special day.
I have to leave and trust my successor
with this lending company
that has been so important for me.
-This--
-Wait, Grandpa! I have something to say.
Jimena, my mom,
is the most hardworking woman of all.
And she's also the best mom.
That's why Jimena Lemus
deserves to be the new CEO.
Howdy!
Come down, you spoiled child!
My daughter isn't spoiled.
Get her down. This is an important event.
Thanks for your support.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for that, kids, but…
Jimena isn't my successor,
Rogelio is.
Santiago!
Rogelio, right?
Nice to meet you. Are you okay?
Don't even try to ruin my moment.
As you can see,
there's nothing a lasso can't fix. Thanks.
Gaby!
Leo! No!
Leo! No! Leo!
Shut it off! No!
Please, don't go!
No, please!
No!
Uncle, what's going on?
Jimena, do something! These are your kids!
Santi, Tania is leaving!
It's now or never!
Tania, you're the star
that lights up my path!
-They're going to--
-They're going to shut it off.
Shut it off!
Sorry.
I get that you wanted to help me,
but you can't throw a lasso at people!
-And get everyone wet!
-Jime, don't blame them.
It wasn't their fault, it was my idea.
How could you throw a lasso
at Rogelio? He's a partner.
He badmouthed the kids
during the entire party.
Stop it! Go to your rooms.
You're so grounded.
Not you, Gabriel.
Come back, I want to talk to you.
Jime, I don't think it's fair for Rogelio
to steal the opportunity of becoming
the CEO of your family's company
only because he's a man.
My dad is will want me
to be the CEO even less
now that you got the entire board wet.
You're right. That wasn't on the plan.
Leo got carried away.
I'm sorry, Gaby,
but this isn't going to work.
Can you button up your shirt?
I can't focus.
I can't fire you
when your six-pack is staring at me.
You want to fire me?
I'm sorry, Gaby, but…
I don't think a cowboy
can be my kids' manny.
I need a…
A woman, right?
My kids need a maternal and loving woman
at home to take care of them.
I can't do it,
as much as I try.
At least, not now.
How funny.
My dad wants me to stay at the ranch
taking care of the pigs,
and yours wants you to stay home
taking care of the kids.
Yes, I guess it's not that easy
to change the world.
At least, not for us.
But for the kids, Jime?
It's different for them.
That's why I love being a manny.
For them.
-Are you going to cry?
-No.
-No, I'm not judging you.
Men don't cry.
-Can I come in, Santi?
-Yes.
Hey,
what did she mean
with "you're so grounded"?
I don't know.
You shouldn't have taken the blame!
Why not? We're a team, aren't we?
Did it help to dress like a cowboy?
No.
She didn't even post a story online.
Being ignored is worse than being trolled.
Maybe it's because
she's three years older than you.
-I can't sleep.
-What's wrong, Leo?
There's a Rogelio
with a pig's head in my closet.
Oh, my! What if I leave my lasso
so you can use it when it shows up again?
-Are you leaving?
-Did my mom fire you?
No, because she never hired me.
Don't you want to stay with us?
Of course I do.
You kids are awesome.
But I have to go back
to Tepa to find another job.
Are you going back to your ranch?
I don't know, Leo.
I messed up with my dad,
and he's not happy with me.
But I promise I will try
to earn his forgiveness,
and then I will come back.
And then I can come visit if you want.
We're going to miss you a lot.
I will miss you too.
I'm going to eat you!
No, Leo!
Jimena, what are you doing here so early?
I'm sorry about what happened yesterday,
but my kids gave me a big lesson,
and more than my kids,
their manny did too.
The manny?
I'll explain later.
I'm here to say
that I'm sorry I'm not a man.
And, I'm sorry that I'm not
who you want me to be
and I'm sorry that I like to work,
and that…
Sometimes I want to cry
when I get frustrated, angry
or whatever.
But being the CEO of this company
has been my dream
and you know I'm the best for the role.
I don't think it's fair that you don't
give me the chance because I'm a woman.
It's not that, sweetheart.
I don't want you to end up alone.
A woman like you scares men away.
I don't need a man by my side, Dad.
That's what you think.
I'm sure of that.
But you know what?
You don't have to worry anymore, because…
I'm here to quit.
I'm going to find other opportunities.
I love you, Dad.
Jimena.
I tried everything
so she would hire me, godmother.
I even cried.
It didn't work.
Gabriel, you can't give up.
Your dad won't forgive you.
I know, but I'm going back to Tepa
and I'll figure it out there.
I don't know who's behind this,
but I won't let them take the ranch.
May God bless you.
I'll let you know when I arrive.
-No!
-Eat it!
-You eat it!
-No.
-Why are you back so early?
-Mom, are you sick?
I quit. I'm unemployed.
I told you.
I quit, and now you're best friends.
Tania said
she had a great time at the party,
and she wants to go out on a date.
Tania is the girl who ignored him.
I promise I will push your wheelchair.
What wheelchair?
Marta, did you put strawberries
in my lunch?
-Yes.
-What about packaged food?
That's not always best for me, mom.
-See you later, mom.
-Bye.
Wow. I hadn't seen them
that happy in a long time.
And that's after Gaby took care of them
for a single day!
ERNESTO: I DECIDED TO GIVE YOU
A CHANCE TO FIGHT FOR THE ROLE.
My dad is considering me
for the role of CEO!
What's going on?
Come back here immediately,
before your dad regrets it.
What? I don't get it.
You're going to compete
for the role with Rogelio.
Hurry, your dad wants
to have a meeting with both of you.
I can't. I don't have anyone
to leave the kids with.
-I need a nanny.
-You had a manny.
I hate what I'm going to say,
but I need that man by my side.
-Where is he?
-He left to the bus station.
You might be able to catch him.
His bus leaves in an hour.
Is my dad waiting for me?
I'll take care of that. Go get the manny.
What should I say? I just fired him.
Whatever is needed.
Tell him you got your period
and were hormonal.
Or you could bring him
this crate with rags that he forgot.
For example.
Anything, Jimena. Hurry up.
Yes. Okay, bye.
Thank you, Martita!
Thanks.
Passengers going to Tepatitlán,
please head to lane seven.
-The bus to Tepatitlán?
-It's about to leave, the second lane.
Please, I just need to deliver this.
It will just take a second.
-Let her in.
-Thank you.
Thanks.
You forgot this crate and rags.
Yes, that's why I got off the bus.
I saw you running with this.
My dad is going to give me
a chance to fight for the role.
I think we can change the world together.
I need you more than ever, Gabriel.
My kids are doing better
since you arrived.
So if you want,
you can stay at the house
with your crate.
Thanks, Jime.
This crate means a lot to me
and to Arete.
Is it okay if Arete…
She would love to stay.
Yes.
I also want her to stay.
Okay, Arete, we have a job now.
You burned down my shed.
What's next, assholes?
If you don't pay,
we're going to burn down your ranch.
Even if you burn down the ranch,
I won't give up!
So, let's see how this goes.
Do you think Jimena
can handle all of this?
Subtitle translation by: Carolina Salazar